# **Vincent Pinas**

Software developer / Student

https://vincentpinas.netlify.app/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/vincent-pinas-a4656b223/ Noord-Holland, Uithoorn (+31) 06 827 942 05

ikbengerrit92@gmail.com https://github.com/vincpinas

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# CSU, Uithoorn—Intern

06-2020 - 07-2020

Worked with both hardware and software to repair desktops and laptops.

# Unc Inc, Amsterdam — Intern

02-2022 - 07-2022

Worked as one of the main front-end developers on the prototype for KennisHub, a platform for students, teachers and experts to connect and share knowledge with each other.

# **GLUE Amsterdam**, Amsterdam — Freelancer

05-2023 - 04-2024

Worked as the main developer on the members.glue.amsterdam website

### **EDUCATION**

# **Amsterdam University of Applied Sciences**, Amsterdam — HBO

August 2023 - TODAY

# Media College Amsterdam, Amsterdam— MBO

August 2020 - juli 2023

# **Veenlanden College**, Mijdrecht — MAVO

September 2015 - Juni 2019

#### **PROGRAMMING SKILLS**

Node.js / Composer Git Html / Css / SCSS JavaScript / TypeScript Php React.js / CraftCMS / WordPress Redux

## **SKILLS**

Web Development Design Photoshop / Adobe Figma

## **LANGUAGES**

Dutch - Native level Engels - Fluent level

## **PROJECTS**

### Kennishub - Online knowledge sharing platform

- Implemented React App to fetch, update and remove posts, topics and users through networking API using Redux.
- Implemented a responsive UI using SCSS.

## Manga.ly - Online manga reader

- Designed and implemented React App that fetches manga through networking API.
- Implemented REST API in PHP for use in the front-end.

## <u>TsChat</u> - Online Bidirectional communication using websockets.

- Designed and implemented a React frontend that makes use of websockets in TypeScript
- Created a backend using Socket.io and Express.js to share data between clients using websockets.

# **GLUE Members** - Members platform for GLUE Amsterdam

- Made a front-end using Twig and JavaScript.
- Created a backend and CMS through CraftCMS
- Implemented a custom map using Mapbox and data from the CMS

#### **ABOUT ME**

#### Who am I?

My name is Vincent Pinas, I'm 21 years old, born in 2003 and I live in Noord-Holland.

Outside of school I like browsing online to explore all kinds of developments which is not only limited to software,

going to the gym and hanging out with friends.

#### What can I do for you?

Since I am aiming to become a front-end developer or a fullstack developer I currently mainly work with React.js, Node.js and PHP development wise. I want to do it all so I'm currently also following a design study.

I'd like to think I am an eager learner so I am happy to learn any new technologies to get something done.

#### My strengths.

I am quite a flexible person, I can usually adapt to my environment quite quickly and get in the flow.

I like to be helpful so if you need anything you can ask me, as long as it's within my abilities of course.

#### Future goals.

I am currently working on both my design skills and development skills to be able to set up my own company later and be able to do it all myself till I set up a team.